elitecme.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy - Elite Learning

#### Thanks for visiting our site. Please take a moment to review our policies on copyright, privacy, and terms and conditions.

## Elite Learning privacy policy

Elite Continuing Education respects and is committed to protecting your privacy, and we use the latest technology to ensure that information you submit remains secure. Only Elite's customer service staff can access personal information, and to further protect the security of your information, members of our staff must use user names and passwords to access company and student information.

This privacy statement applies to all websites and domains owned by Elite Continuing Education. It covers personally identifiable information, anonymous data collection and aggregate reporting. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name or personal identity.

## What We Collect

We collect information you voluntarily provide to us through requests for course materials and the completion of courses; e-mails; and to handle support issues. This may include your name, address, phone, fax, e-mail address, license number, billing information, transaction and credit card information.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. While we do gather information on IP addresses (the Internet address of your computer) of visitors and log which parts of the site you visit, we do not link that IP address to any personal information. Like many other commercial web sites, Elite Continuing Education may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site and to facilitate your use of our online products and services.

## How We Use Personal Information

We use your personal information to complete your purchases, handle your requests for assistance or support, and so you can provide feedback in an online survey. We also use it to keep records up-to-date and to notify you via periodic e-mails of technical issues, specials and promotions and other related product and service information. If you do wish to receive e-mails from us, you may opt out by calling us at [1-888-857-6920](tel:8888576920) or by e-mailing [office@elitecme.com](mailto:office@elitecme.com).

## Who We Share Information With

We never sell or rent your personal information and will not share it with third parties. The only exception to this policy involves legal issues. Elite Continuing Education may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law (for example, when served with a subpoena) or regulation; or to comply with legal processes served on the site, such as reports of course completion to your state's licensing agency; or to protect the rights and property of Elite Continuing Education.

## Safeguards

Elite Continuing Education is committed to data security for any information collected on our site. We have put in place appropriate security measures at our physical site to protect against theft, misuse or alteration of any information we have collected from you. Online, we offer state-of-the-art measures including Thawte for SSL encryption for your protection. If you wish to purchase a product but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a customer service representative over the telephone. Simply call [1-888-857-6920](tel:8888576920).

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Our customer service staff members may access your data, but credit card information is redacted so that even they are able to see only the last four digits of your credit card number.

Credit card numbers are used for processing payment only and are not used for any other purpose. Our efforts to protect against credit card fraud help protect your financial data security as well. As part of real-time payment processing, Elite Continuing Education subscribes to a fraud management service.

## About the cookies

Our websites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information. They do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes only. The statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

Elite Continuing Education websites use "cookies" -- identifiers that our web server could send to your computer in order to identify the computer being used for the duration of the session. They cannot generate programs or viruses on your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can be read only by the web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you wish. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use some interactive features of Elite Continuing Education products.

## Problems or Complaints with the Elite Continuing Education Privacy Policy

We value your comments and opinions. If you have questions, comments or a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [office@elitecme.com](mailto:office@elitecme.com).
